http://www.thehairstyler.com/privacy-policy-terms-of-use

Terms of Use and Privacy Policy
TheHairStyler.com Web Site Terms & Conditions of Use and Privacy Policy
1. Terms
By accessing this web site, you are agreeing to be bound by these web site Terms and Conditions of Use, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this web site are protected by applicable copyright and trade mark law.
2. Use License
Permission is granted to temporarily download one copy of the materials (information or software) on TheHairStyler.com's web site for personal, non-commercial transitory viewing only. This is the grant of a license, not a transfer of title, and under this license you may not: 1. modify or copy the materials; 2. use the materials for any commercial purpose, or for any public display (commercial or non-commercial); 3. attempt to decompile or reverse engineer any software contained on TheHairStyler.com's web site; 4. remove any copyright or other proprietary notations from the materials; or 5. transfer the materials to another person or "mirror" the materials on any other server.
This license shall automatically terminate if you violate any of these restrictions and may be terminated by TheHairStyler.com at any time. Upon terminating your viewing of these materials or upon the termination of this license, you must destroy any downloaded materials in your possession whether in electronic or printed format.
3. Disclaimer
The materials on TheHairStyler.com's web site are provided "as is". TheHairStyler.com makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties, including without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights. Further, TheHairStyler.com does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its Internet web site or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site.
4. Limitations
In no event shall TheHairStyler.com or its suppliers be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption,) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on TheHairStyler.com's Internet site, even if TheHairStyler.com or a TheHairStyler.com authorized representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you.
5. Revisions and Errata
The materials appearing on TheHairStyler.com's web site could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. TheHairStyler.com does not warrant that any of the materials on its web site are accurate, complete, or current. TheHairStyler.com may make changes to the materials contained on its web site at any time without notice. TheHairStyler.com does not, however, make any commitment to update the materials.
6. Links
TheHairStyler.com has not reviewed all of the sites linked to its Internet web site and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by TheHairStyler.com of the site. Use of any such linked web site is at the user's own risk.
7. Site Terms of Use Modifications
TheHairStyler.com may revise these terms of use for its web site at any time without notice. By using this web site you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these Terms and Conditions of Use.
8. Governing Law
Any claim relating to TheHairStyler.com's web site shall be governed by the laws of the State of NSW without regard to its conflict of law provisions.
Privacy Policy of TheHairStyler.com
Information about our Organisation and Web site Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of an organisation like TheHairStyler.com.
We are based in Australia; our principal activity is: Website
Our privacy policy covers TheHairStyler.com and its Web site:
Organisation Name: TheHairStyler.com
Address: PO Box 808
City, Zip: Narellan , 2567
State: NSW
Country: Australia
Controller: Director, Public Relations
Web Sites(s): https://www.thehairstyler.com
Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access
You can access our Web site home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data.
Privacy Settings
When you register with TheHairStyler.com you create your own profile in accordance with our privacy settings.
(i) We may occasionally use your name and email address to send you notifications regarding new services offered by TheHairStyler.com that we think you may find valuable.
(ii) Profile information submitted to TheHairStyler.com that includes your favorites and photos you have uploaded to the Virtual Hairstyler cannot be viewed by anybody except you.
(iii) Profile information is used by TheHairStyler.com primarily to be presented back to and edited by you when you access the service, and to aid your exchange of hairstyling ideas.
(iv) TheHairStyler.com may send you service-related announcements from time to time through the general operation of the web site.
(v) TheHairStyler.com may use information in your profile without identifying you as an individual to third parties. We do this for purposes such as aggregating users' tastes in order to customise advertisements and promotions on the web site. We believe this personalisation benefits you.
The Services and Links of Our Website
Our Web site enables you to post information to be accessed by others. When you do so, other visitors may collect your data. Our Web site also includes a link to:
Google Inc.
Total Beauty Media, Inc.
Kontera.com
Such third party Web service providers may collect personal data about our visitors.
Automatic Collection of Information
We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals. We do not use cookies to store personal data nor do we link non-personal information stored in cookies with personal data about specific individuals.
Data Collection and Purpose Specification
We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services. We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organisations. We do not collect or use personal data for any purpose other than that indicated below. If we wish to use your personal data for new purposes, we offer you the means to consent to those new purposes:
by indicating in a box at the point on the site where personal data is collected
by sending an email: info@thehairstyler.com
by visiting this url: https://www.thehairstyler.com/website-faq
Disclosure and Visitor Choice
We do not disclose your personal data to our subsidiaries or other organisations.
Confidentiality/Security
We do not give visitors to our Web site the option of using a secure transmission method to send us their personal data. We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from:
unauthorised access
improper use or disclosure
unauthorised modification
unlawful destruction or accidental loss
All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data. We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation.
Access to the personal data we may hold about you
You can ask us, by:
sending an email: info@thehairstyler.com
We do not provide our visitors with a readable copy of the personal data that we keep about them. We do not allow our visitors to challenge the data that we hold about them. We do reserve the right to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data.
Privacy Compliance
Our privacy policy is compliant with the following instrument: Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) There are no global or regional regulatory or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organisation. We cannot demonstrate that our privacy policy accords with the privacy instrument.
Privacy Support
If you have an enquiry or concern about our privacy policy, please contact:
Name/designation: Director, Public Relations
Address: PO Box 808, Narellan - NSW, 2567
Email address: info@thehairstyler.com
URL: https://www.thehairstyler.com
We do not recommend another means by which visitors' concerns may be addressed.
Personal data collected and purposes for which they are used
Primary Personal Data
Individuals voluntarily supply their name, gender, address and email. The Web site uses this information for the techincal administration of the web site, customer administration and marketing (email address). The Web site uses this information, as well as information about phone/fax numbers and other, collected from public records and/or private organisations, for the technical administration of the web site, research and development, customer administration, marketing and trading in personal data.
Business Information
The Web site uses information about an individual's employer, job, address, email, phone or other, collected from public records or private organisations, for the technical administration of the website, research and development, customer administration, marketing, and trading in personal data.
Other Personal Details and Profiling Data
Individuals voluntarily supply their physical description and information about their lifestyle and personal tastes. The Web site uses this information for the technical administration of the web site, customer administration and marketing. The web site uses information about individuals' personal details, family characteristics, education and skills, financial resources and other, collected from public records and/or private organisations, for the technical administration of the web site, research and development, customer administration, marketing and trading in personal data.
Security
TheHairStyler.com uses Thawte to provide a secure environment for your personal details.
Membership
Membership with TheHairStyler.com is absolutely FREE and we do not charge any monthly or hidden fees! For more info please visit our signup page.
All memberships can be canceled at any time from your account.
Photo Upload Policy
By ticking the photo upload policy box in the add photo wizard of the Virtual Hairstyler, you certify that you have the right to use any photos that you upload to your account and that they do not violate the terms and conditions of TheHairStyler.com. To view our photo specifications, please click here.
Send Us Your Feedback
Your suggestions and ideas are important to us.
Copyright © 2000 - 2020 TheHairStyler.com Pty Ltd.
All Rights reserved.
Powered by ProofFactor - Social Proof Notifications
